brunoscholz@yahoo.de

https://brunoscholz.vercel.app/

Bruno Ribeiro Scholz

ABOUT ME

Skilled life-long student and developer with 15+ years of experience in diverse fields and an entrepreneurial view, my goal is always to create value by generating intelligent solutions that fulfill client's needs. I like situations that require the use of multiple skills and critical thinking.

EXPERIENCE

WUNDERMAN THOMPSON TECH / VML

Backend Engineer - Vue, PHP, Drupal

January 2022 - Current

Fullstack Drupal / Backend Engineer. Working in big drupal projects like FitnessFirst and AB-INBEV.

POSSIBLE / WUNDERMAN THOMPSON TECH

Frontend Engineer - Angular, React, Drupal

January 2021 - Current

Frontend Engineer. Held a few client technical meetings and some solo projects. Several projects for clients like Siemens, DWS and SporTV.

OCTTON

Co-Founder & Game Developer - Unity3D(C#), Angular, Python, PHP, Mysql

February 2014 - August 2016

Creating products directed to corporate training, advergames for business fairs and educational games.

Banco do Brasil

PHP, MySql, VBA

May 2006 - February 2014

Worked together with engineering and logistics management in Manaus (AM) in the development of a dashboard for cost control in building and renovation projects.

ABBRA

```
Developer - PHP, MySql
```

```
April 2004 - May 2006
```

Development of dynamic processes, from contract to complete legal process with customer leads, batch research and verification in court databases for more than one million potential clients.

EDUCATION

ACQUIA CERTIFICATION

DRUPAL 10 Developer - Drupal, PHP, Javascript

2024

UNIVERSIDADE POSITIVO, Curitiba

```
Digital Games - Unity3D, 3DSMax, C#, Javascript
2013 - 2015 (incomplete)
```

UNIVERSIDADE FEDERAL DO AMAZONAS, Manaus

```
Computer Science - Haskell, Python
2011 - 2013 (incomplete)
```

UNIVERSIDADE TECNOLÓGICA FEDERAL DO PARANÁ, Curitiba

Electrical Engineering - Electronics and Telecommunication - c, c++

2003 - 2006 (incomplete)